ANDREW LEVANDOSKI

T: (570) 690-5039 E: 1alevandoski@gmail.com 22 Rice Court Dallas, PA 18612

Objective

To gain experience in software development through an internship involving critical thinking, technical exercise, and collaborative problem solving. To fuse experiences and interests in computer software, algorithm development, and computational analysis to develop powerful software and generate data-intensive insights.

Experience

Proscia, Inc.

May 2016 - Current

Designed and built a cloud-based digital pathology platform used by physicians and researchers around the world using Jade, SCSS, and JavaScript. Currently works as a front-end developer on features that expand and improve the platform to accommodate a growing user base.

Laboratory of Ocular Biomechanics, University of Pittsburgh

April 2015 – October 2015

Developed and implemented algorithms as plugins to automate and more easily facilitate research using Fiji, an open source image processing package based on ImageJ. Conducted research analyzing the effects of increased intraocular pressure on collagen crimp around the eye using polarized light microscopy and image analysis.

Education

University of Pittsburgh, Pittsburgh, PA

2014 - 2018

B.S., Computer Science, Economics Cumulative GPA: 3.525/4.0

Relevant Coursework: Algorithm Design, Algorithm Implementation, Data Structures, Systems Software, Formal Methods, Discrete Mathematics, Web Applications, Operating Systems, Network Security and Cryptography

Pennsylvania Governor's School for the Sciences, Carnegie Mellon University, Pittsburgh, PA

2013

Instruction in computer science, mathematics, physics, biology, and chemistry with emphasis on collaborative learning and team research. Completed research in the fields of computational biology and electrical engineering.

Wyoming Seminary Upper School, Kingston, PA

2010 - 2014

Cumulative GPA: 4.0/4.0

Recipient of Harry W. and Emma R. Ruggles Award for Outstanding Graduate, National Merit Finalist, 2014

Technical Skills

Languages: Java, C, Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MIPS Assembly

Platforms: Windows, OS X, Unix

Other Skills: Version Control Systems (Git), Microsoft Office, Mathematica, Corel

Professional Development

University of Pittsburgh Cycling Executive Board, Business Director

2016 (Current)

Responsible for sponsorship acquisition and budget allocation. Competitor in the ECCC.

Emerging Leaders Program

2014

Leadership development highlighting fundamentals of leadership. Sponsored by the University of Pittsburgh.

Junior Leadership Wilkes-Barre

2013 - 2014

Leadership, communications, professional development, and community engagement program. Organized a 5k road race benefitting the Janet Weis Children's Hospital (Danville, PA). Sponsored by Leadership Wilkes-Barre.